hi just a quick announcement video it's
a survey and giveaway time again yes I
got five uh items to give away bm235
bm786 BML 121 GW a hvp 70 high voltage
probe and a CP
um 2100 B
current probe
awesome and if you want to win them all
you have to do is partake in the eev
blog survey last time I did this was
back in well maybe April or something
was it um or early March uh 2017. so I
think it's long overdue for another
survey and the results from these are
actually fascinating and of course at
the end of the survey I'll give it like
I don't know a couple of days or
whatever for people uh to respond maybe
even a week for people to respond and
then we'll I'll do a video analyzing the
data because that's absolutely
fascinating so I'll link in the previous
one down here where I go through all of
the results from my previous survey so I
want to see if things have changed if my
audience has changed my uh you know the
type of things that you want to see on
my channel have changed and things like
that so I had 12 000 responses last time
awesome
um let's see if we can beat that again
and if you do the survey optionally you
don't have to if you just want to do the
survey thank you very much but if you do
want to leave your email address and
your name at the end you will actually
go into the draw for
stop my recording did I um a damaged
bm235
um there were five different items to
give away so I'll just give those away
randomly
in a separate video so
after it's done so you can either
participate in that or not if you don't
want to win and you just want to
contribute that's great thank you very
much so anyway
um it's I'm gonna do almost identical to
the survey that I did last time uh and
see if we uh can get you know and
compare the results to last time see if
things have changed so I'm basically
asking for uh country here and then what
types of videos would uh would you what
type of videos do you like actually
watching or do you actually watch and
you can see all the different types of
content that I have I don't know of a
channel that does more different types
of content than mine it's insane like
count them like these are the different
types of videos that I do so people
complain that one good thing about this
survey is that when people complain that
I'm not doing this type of video or this
it's because well either people don't
want it or I can't possibly do them all
because look at all these different
types and people are there's people that
like every single one of these types and
I can't do them all the time anyway and
then there's optional ones about what
you do you really want to see more of
because I I don't have I've only have X
number of hours in the day I can only
produce X number of videos so which ones
do you really so be selective which ones
do you really want to see more of and
I'll take that into account and possibly
um do more of those types of videos and
also because I love feedback if you
simply must complain which ones do you
you're so offended that I'm spending my
time even making these videos like how
dare I um so yeah tell me which ones um
it's they're all the same categories and
then uh basically what level of the
industry you're at
um pretty much so yeah that's just nice
to know sort of where you're at
um what do you think about the current
video frequencies just right and do I
need more do I need less High more
highly polished what do you think uh
video length same question as last time
and and uh this is a new one and I did
this on my as a poll on my I don't know
I think I just did on the main Channel
but I thought I'd include in the survey
here and this one's relatively important
given that I have so dozens and dozens
of different type of content do you want
to see those potentially separated into
different channels eev blog channels
like at the moment if you don't know
I've got three channels the eev Vlog
Channel which is the main Channel evlog
2. just about to hit a hundred thousand
but I can't seem to damn well do it it's
been sitting on like ninety seven and a
half thousand for like ever
um so subscribe to EV blog too where I
just put more random stuff and less
polished uh content I've also got eev
academy uh sorry eev discover as well
where I do like you know interesting
site visits or other uh types of videos
I've got a uh how to I did some um my
own research on uh proving that we
actually landed on the moon so that's a
Fascinate maybe I'll link that video in
if you haven't seen it it's over on EV
discover I think it's really quite cool
so um do you not like these second
channels at all do you want Emmy to put
absolutely everything regardless of how
crap it is on the main Channel or are
you happening do you only watch the main
Channel you just don't care about
anything else
um are you happy with the current three
channels that I've got or would you like
a specific channel for tutorials for
example because I'm I got a lot of
tutorial videos out there and I'm
producing seen more in sort of like a
series if you haven't noticed I'm
producing like starting from Basics and
getting up and up through like almost an
entire course type thing would you like
to see that on a separate eev Academy
channel uh for example
um would you like just an EV dumpster
Channel where I just do dumpster diving
videos and you know if you only like the
dumpster videos would you like to see or
put in something else uh and would you
like to see any more categories is if I
don't have enough would you like me to
see any more categories and then uh yeah
put just put your name in the draw if
you want to enter the draw so yeah um
let's have a look and see what the
responses are because it'll be
absolutely fascinating like it was last
time so thank you very much in advance
for those who link down below to the
survey and uh most of the question I
think there's only one one of them two
of them that are compulsory the rest are
optional if you don't want to answer
them but I really appreciate everyone
entering you must have called I believe
you have to I think you have to have a
Google account to do it I can't remember
it's using Google forms so I'm not
entirely sure but anyway there'll be a
link down below but considering Motors
everyone's watching this on YouTube
anyway unless you're on my Odyssey
Channel which has got more than 60 000
subscribers you probably got a YouTube
account anyway but I'm not sure if you
actually need a YouTube account to do it
anyway if you do sorry about that it's
just a convenient way to do it so thanks
in advance for the survey and good luck
in the contest if you choose to give
away if you choose to enter thanks catch
you next time